Excuse me, Dr. Gablehauser,
are you busy?
- Well, actually...
- Sheldon, he's just doodling. Get in here.
- Dr. Gablehauser.
- Dr. Cooper.
(Mrs Cooper:)Let's go, baby, we're losing daylight.
(Sheldon:)Um...
(Sheldon:)As you know, several weeks ago
in our first encounter...
(Sheldon:)...we may have gotten off
on the wrong foot...
(Sheldon:)...when I called you an idiot.
(Sheldon:)And I just wanted to say
that I was wrong...
(Sheldon:)...to point it out.
(Gablehouser(to Mrs Cooper):)I'm sorry, we haven't been introduced.
- Dr. Eric Gablehauser.
- Mary Cooper, Sheldon's mom.
Now, that's impossible. You must've
had him when you were a teenager.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, aren't you sweet. His father's dead.
- Recently?
- Long enough.
(Sheldon:)Please.
(Gablehouser(indicating chair):)Sheldon, shouldn't you be working?